Rey Michael Estela

Licensed Civil Engineer

ASP.net Core entry level developer

reymichael.estela@gmail.com

Attps://www.linkedin.com/in/rey-estela-489939150/

0977-190-2388

PROFILE

Microsoft Power Platform active user, with on-going exposure of ASP.net Core Console app development skillset. High proficiency to Excel Formulas and environment, exposed to Excel VBA. Comfortable working Data tables and dashboards. Familiar with JSON Schema, SQL, HTML and CSS.

Professional Working experience of more than 8yrs years. Experienced in Vertical Construction, Architectural, Flood control infrastructures, Real Estate and Telecom + TowerCo, Adapted in ISO Standard compliances and documentations, High Proficiency to Project Management.

Skills and Certifications

ASP.net Core	HTML / CSS	Excel VBA	Microsoft Forms	PowerApps	WAH Certified	I	BOSH
C#	SQL	Excel Advanced	Power Automate	SketchUp PRO	Google Earth PRO	ľ	Project Management
JSON	Power Platform	Sharepoint List	PowerBI	AutoCAD	COSH SO2	ľ	

- **Change Management in an Agile Environment
- **Certificate of Completion: Excel Essential for Real World

Work Experiences

Skytowers Infra Incorporated

Assistant Manager for Engineering and Projects

Jan 11, 2021 to Present

- Project Management and Main Technical Single Point of Contact (SPOC)

 Major technical designs and assessments
 - ✓ Full-Turnkey / CME / SAQ / Grid Vendors
 - ✓ Safety protocols and Working at Heights guidelines
- Standard Timeline and deadlines of Project Milestones
- ☑ Bill of Quantities and Variation works
- monitoring and recording of milestones for vast amount of project sites

Milestones / Highlights

- Full-Turnkey for 41 4-Legged Self-Support Towers
- 9 32mtr/40mtr Greenfield Self-Supporting-Tower Projects

Microsoft Forms	Power Automate	SketchUp PRO	Google Earth PRO	Excel Advanced
Sharepoint List	PowerBI	AutoCAD	Power Platform	Project Management

Hammertime Construction Incorporated

Site Civil Engineer II Feb 2020 to Nov. 2020

Project Management for a 9 – Storey, 1-hectare building Project

- Technical guidance to Contractors and Foremen
- ✓ Weighted Progress work versus Cashflow Diagram
- Assess accomplishments (Daily, Weekly, Monthly)
- ✓ Contract Awarding, Billing Assessment and Notice to proceed
- ✓ Deadline Enforcement
- ✓ Project Management Collaboration
- ✓ Technical assessment, scope of work, accomplishment

Milestones / Highlights

- 9-Storey, 1 hectare coverage Religious Convention Bldg.
- Ultra high-ceiling & Granite finish walls
- Excel VBA Excel Advanced Project Ma
- ☑ 3000 units of Cinema sitting chairs, approx. 500 units of Fiber-glass Panels
- ✓ Full Cinematic Convention Floors

Tokwing Construction Corporation

Project Engineer

Assess accomplishments (Daily, Weekly, Monthly)

Jan 2016 to March 2019

Jan. 2015 to Nov. 2015

- Site Project Management
 - ▼ Technical guidance to Contractors and Foremen
 - ✓ Weighted Progress work versus Cashflow Diagram
- ✓ Contract Awarding, Billing Assessment and Notice to proceed

Milestones / Highlights

- ☑ Divine Grace Medical Center bldg. (9-storey Medical Arts Bldg.)
- Pasig-Marikina River Channel Improvement Project (CP-6).

Excel VBA Ex

Excel Advanced Project Management

EC Structural Composites Incorporated

AutoCAD Operator

✓ As-built drafter

Milestones / Highlights

4-Storey Office/Commercial Bldg As-built drawings

A Flood control DPWHproject for the River Channel of Marikina River via Retaining Inverted T-Wall reinforcedwith Concrete Pile foundation

Education Character References

Primary and Secondary: Roosevelt College Cainta (SY 1998 to 2009)

Benjamin Zoghi | Director of Operation & Business Development

4 0939-916-5416

Tertiary: Far Eastern University (FEU) - Institute of Technology (SY 2010 to 2015)

Gloria Dazo | Director of Finance & Corp. Support Services

Bachelor of Science in Civil Engineering

0917-118-5811